[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How are the young Box turtles classified according to their diet, which differs from the diet of mature Box turtles?", "correct_answer": "Carnivores", "incorrect_answers": ["Specialized eaters", "Omnivores", "Herbivores"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie starred Leonardo DiCaprio, Billy Zane and Kathy Bates.", "correct_answer": "Titanic", "incorrect_answers": ["Whats Eating Gilbert Grape?", "Misery", "Pet Semetary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie adaptation of a Broadway musical won eleven Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "West Side Story", "incorrect_answers": ["My Fair Lady", "Oliver", "Gigi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Europe and Latin America, a league is a measurement unit of what physical quantity?", "correct_answer": "Distance", "incorrect_answers": ["Volume", "Weight", "Speed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Die Hard, after detective McClane gets out, a newspaper reporter tries to interview him. Who punches the reporter in the face?", "correct_answer": "McLanes wife", "incorrect_answers": ["Sgt. Powell", "McClane", "An FBI agent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who were the faithful soldiers to the Imperial Army in the Star Wars movies?", "correct_answer": "Stormtroopers", "incorrect_answers": ["Battle Droids", "Marines", "Super Battle Droids"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This modern-day European country, once ruled by Khan Asparuh, was acknowledged by the Byzantine Empire in 681.", "correct_answer": "Republic of Bulgaria", "incorrect_answers": ["Republic of Macedonia", "Republic of Romania", "Czech Republic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the blood cells called thrombocytes responsible for?", "correct_answer": "Blood clotting", "incorrect_answers": ["Defence against bacteria and viruses", "Transporting carbon dioxide", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first play Shakespeare wrote?", "correct_answer": "Henry VI, Part One", "incorrect_answers": ["The Tempest", "A Midsummers Night Dream", "Hamlet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 100 people, how many would be female?", "correct_answer": "52", "incorrect_answers": ["60", "40", "46"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of these animals have large ears (relative to their size) except one.", "correct_answer": "Polar bears", "incorrect_answers": ["Foxes", "Bats", "Elephants"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 2007 movie, based on a true story, ends with a note that Erin Gruwell successfully brought many of her students to graduation and college?", "correct_answer": "Freedom Writers", "incorrect_answers": ["The Ron Clark Story", "The Diary of Anne Frank", "Dangerous Minds"]}]